SO, I I'M JACK. UH, I I live in London
quite locally. Um, I'm I'm quite posh,
as probably most of you have already
gauged.
[\h__\h] for it, though. You get quite a lot
of stick for being posh, but you know,
it's like I always say, sticks and
stones, they break my bones. But
whatever. I'm with ber. Um,
I am posh. I'm not like not like
rightwing though. Not not not prejudice,
not homophobic.
Well, I guess I'm homophobic in the same
sense that I'm arachnophobic. I'm not
scared of spiders. I'm not scared of
gays, though I would probably scream if
I saw one in my bath.
[applause]
And you know, I really I'm young. I'm
not like I'm not like one of like you
know your regular youth I guess cuz
people are afraid of young people now
aren't they? And and I'm afraid of young
people as well. But I I forget what I'm
meant to be afraid of cuz it seems to
change with young people. If you read
the tabloids like one minute you get
it's the young people cuz like knife
crime and gun crime hoodies as they're
going to stab you. All of that stuff.
Next minute they're all fat and they're
overweight and it's the obesity
epidemic. And I'm confused. I don't know
what I'm meant TO BE SCARED OF ANYMORE.
I'M WORRIED TO WALK DOWN THE STREET
UNLESS I'M ATTACKED BY A FAT KID WITH A
KNIFE and a fork.
[applause]
I want to stay fit. I want to be good at
things like fitness and I want to be
healthy. I want to be healthy. But I've
never been good at it. You know, even
when I was at school, I hated pee. It
was my I hated PE so much at school.
Mainly because of my PE teacher was
complete [\h__\h] His name was Mr.
Walton. He was from Sith Iitha and he
was a lumbering hulk of protein shake
and unresolved childhood issues which he
took out of me every week. He was
horrible to me. He humiliated me every
lesson. Right. And I remember I remember
one class, right? Okay. He tried to get
us to do a bleep test which I refused to
do cuz we weren't living in Nazi
Germany. Ironically, an environment in
which he would have thrived. And he was
shouting at me, pushing me, trying to
embarrass me and humiliate me. I'm quite
a sensitive soul. I couldn't hack it.
Eventually, I flipped. HE WAS LIKE,
"COME ON, JACK. PUSH YOURSELF NOW.
EMBRACE THE BURN. LOOK AT MY BODY, JACK.
HOW DO YOU THINK I GOT TO WHERE I AM
TODAY?" I DON'T KNOW. OPPRESSING BLACK
PEOPLE
cuz he thought HE WAS A MOTIVATOR. HE
THOUGHT THE STUFF THAT HE WAS SAYING WAS
INSPIRATIONAL to the children. It
wasn't. It was psychotic. And it never
MADE ANY SENSE AS WELL. I REMEMBER ONCE
RIGHT WE WERE PLAYING basketball and
just in the middle of the game he blew
his whistle and in front OF EVERYONE
JUST SHOUTED AT ME THE PROBLEM WITH YOU
JACK IS ALL FART AND NO POO. WELL WHEN I
FART [screaming] I FOLLOW THROUGH AND
SOMETIMES THERE'S BLOOD
but I tried at school. I just could
never do very well. But I always think
right if you weren't very good at school
there's always one thing that everyone
that wasn't good at school can hold on
to and we need to hold on to this AND
THAT IS THAT EVERY school all over the
world in every class there was always
that person that was better than
everyone else. Yeah. That got into all
the sports teams that was in the school
play that had a girlfriend. Mr. Perfect.
You can hold on to the fact that yeah
they were Mr. Perfect at school and
everyone resented them and they were so
great but in later life Mr. perfect will
have made his mistakes. He will have
screwed things up. And now with
Facebook, you can find the bastard.
You can hunt HIM DOWN AND LOOK AT HIS
PHOTOGRAPHS AND REALIZE, "YEAH, YOU WERE
MR. PERFECT AT SCHOOL, BUT NOW SOMEONE'S
PUT ON A LITTLE BIT OF WEIGHT. NOW
SOMEONE'S LOST THEIR JOB AND THEY'RE
SLEEPING IN THE BACK OF THEIR CAR. SO
SCREW YOU, ROBBIE WESTLAKE."
AND IT'S NOT JUST YOU CAN ALSO FIND
PEOPLE THAT DIDN'T WANT TO HAVE SEX WITH
YOU AT SCHOOL, THAT REJECTED you at
school cuz they were better than you at
school. And you can find them on
Facebook as well. And you can hunt them
down and look through their photographs
and do what us perverts like TO REFER TO
AS THE REVENGE. WE'VE GOT PEOPLE from
Hob, haven't we? Got Hugh. Where's Hugh?
Hugh, how you doing? You're a fantastic
actor. You've been RSC and everything.
You've been in Holbe for a long time,
right? So, I have a theory that if
someone had a heart attack over here, we
could whisk you over and just suck all
of the drama out of the situation.
We had the Commonwealth Games in Glasgow
this year. A great choice of venue. A
place where people think that hepatitis
B is a vitamin.
I don't really trust these big sporting
occasions. You know, the Olympics, a lot
of that stuff is just for rich people.
Dress, yaching. I don't remember that at
school.
ying tomorrow class. So remember, bring
in your boats.
A lot of people find the Parolympics
inspiring. I just find it depressing. I
can't throw a discus and I've got arms.
Oscar Ptorius. Pistorius to me sounds
like a spell that Harry Potter would say
to make your legs drop off.
When he gets out of jail, his next
girlfriend is going to get ready in a
hurry.
>> Thought you were RUNNING A BATH. NO, I
JUST THREW SOME DUNGAREES ON. LET'S GO.
I hope a jail bully steals his legs,
walks about being 9'6.
I don't like the Commonwealth cuz the
Commonwealth is the old British Empire.
It's called the Commonwealth because
Britain stole all those countries wealth
and then went come on.
The whole empire was founded on cocaine.
Everybody was on cocaine. The remedies
had cocaine IN THEM. QUEEN VICTORIA WAS
ON COCAINE AND NOT THE [\h__\h] YOU TAKE.
YOU'VE NEVER DONE a line and gone, let's
invade India.
We had the referendum up in Scotland
that was won by the no campaign and
Alistister Darling I thought it'd be
good if when he won Alistister Darlin's
eyebrows had finally turned into
butterflies
and he wasn't even able to look
surprised about it.
David Beckham sent the people of
Scotland an open letter. An open letter
cuz he couldn't work out how to get it
into the envelope. People
said during the campaign that I was
anti-English. I couldn't be more pro-
English. I thought the best thing for
independence would have been if England
had won the World Cup cuz you would have
been so unbearable that we would have to
leave.
Whatever happens next, I think it's
important that Scotland does something
that puts England on the back foot.
Something that England won't expect. And
the last thing that you're expecting is
for us to form an Islamic caliphate.
I independent Scotland. We can do this.
I used to be not exactly ashamed of my
blackness, but I never wanted to do
anything that could be seen as
stereotypically black. And it followed
me all my life. So when I was younger,
when I was at school, if I was ever in
PE and a basketball would come flying at
top speed towards my face, instead of
catching that basketball in the air,
dribbling it towards the nearest net,
and slam dunking the thing, as I
naturally would,
I just let it hit me in the face and
roll away.
When I got older, I made a lot of
friends, mainly white friends, and we
started going to the club. Are you
familiar with the club?
Not the club. Duck Club at the end of D
Street. Whenever I went to the club and
I was dancing with a group of friends, I
would deliberately dance less well on
purpose
so that the white people wouldn't be
intimidated.
There'd always be one other black person
in the corner of the room, arms folded,
looking at me like, "You're
disrespecting yourself."
When meanwhile, I'll be in the middle of
the dance floor just moving like Miley
Cyrus.
I tried so hard. I tried so hard to pass
as white. I did all the white things. I
bought pesto.
I said tiss you.
I got really dangerously into Jamie T.
I am talking about the era of Jamie T,
Pete Daert,
Jack Pñat.
Jedwish.
I spent my late teens, arguably the
sexiest part of one's teens,
just sort of lusting over these gurning
predators.
Like, imagine we were me. You'll be at a
house party with an edgy white boy and
he'd have the whole edgy boy starter
kit. He'd have the skinny jeans, rolly
[\h__\h] unacceptable bo.
He'd be talking always about one of his
two favorite subjects, which is always
either dubstep or himself.
And sitting on the window sill, and
finally you'd pluck up the courage to
just cut him off mid aneote, put your
hand on his shoulder, look him in the
eye, and be like, "Mate, I love you."
And then he'd look at you and you'd look
at him and you'd lean in for a kiss and
then he just sort of
thumb MDMA into your mouth,
man. But that was it. You were like,
"Wow,
I think he really likes me."
Oh my god, white guys. I spent half my
life lusting after unsuitable white
guys. Have we GOT ANY WHITE GUYS IN?
>> Come on, guys. Cheer louder. We know how
much you get paid.
There you are. OF COURSE, YOU WHITE guys
are here because you are everywhere.
You're in the White House. YOU'RE IN THE
BIG BANKS. You're in all the fancy court
cases. You're killing it.
Sometimes, literally.
But I don't want anyone to think I'm
having a go because I genuinely adore
white guys. Love your work, Ed Sheeran.
Amazing.
I haven't got anything against white men
apart from obviously
everything it is that they've done.
>> Some of my best friends,
some of my best friends are white men.
My mother is a white man.
Incredible to think, isn't it?
But the Chinese language
started off as English in England.
Then one person whispered it to another
person.
Bit of a weird day today.
I found a hole in the back of my
wardrobe.
I went through to a strange and
mysterious land
where my neighbor was sitting in the
bath.
What else can I tell you about myself? I
like my tea. Like my women
big, black, and with a penguin.
Obviously,
I'm Caucasian. It's my mom's from a city
in Ireland and my dad's Japanese.
[applause]
Couldn't sleep last night. I was too
hot. Then the smoke alarm went off.
Put it on snooze.
Then the phone went off. Picked it up.
Voice said, "Can you speak?" I said,
"How did you think this conversation was
going to work?"
And I recognized the voice of my mother,
the very woman who taught me to speak in
the first place.
She said, "Listen,
it's your dad."
I said, "That is the worst impression."
Do you ever have a conversation with
someone and towards the end they say,
"Well, I'll let you go."
You think, "Yeah, thanks.
Oh, I see what you're saying. You're
trying to make me think that you think
that I've got better things to do. In
reality, you're saying that you've got
better things to do. Well, next time
someone says to you, I'll let you go,
say, no.
Shut the door.
If they make a sudden dive for the
window, grab them by their ankles as
they're dangling four stories over the
car park, screaming, "This has all been
a terrible mistake." say, "Okay, I'll
let you go."
So, it turns out not all horses are
Trojan horses.
I know that now.
That was a messy afternoon.
Health and safety. That's a minefield,
isn't it? Don't tell them.
I used to work in IKEA selling over
7,000 different items. Give me a number
between 1 and 7,000. I'll tell you about
it.
>> Eight. Sorry, out of stock.
Well, it's not easy traveling around all
the time, being on the road. Oh, no. The
AA RA green flag. Don't get me started.
>> [applause]
>> I've got a good relationship with me,
mom. Uh, you know, sometimes in comedy
you laugh at things cuz it's familiar,
cuz it's a shared experience. Sometimes
you laugh because you're just glad
you're not me.
See if this has happened to anybody
else. Uh, whenever I'm on the phone to
me mom, it always makes me need a poo.
Give us a woo if that's happened to you.
Yeah. See, I've looked into it. It's a
It's a closeness issue. It means that me
and those people who wooed, we love our
moms more than the rest of you that love
yours. I love my mom so much, it makes
me [\h__\h]
Try getting that on a balloon for
Mother's Day.
Thank God for Moon Pig.
But I bought a house quite recently. I
uh I wanted to buy a house cuz I'd lived
in flats for 16 years and I really
missed going upstairs to bed.
Not through the kitchen,
upstairs to bed. But I was sitting only
a few months later upstairs in bed quite
smuggly just thinking, "This is the
life. I've arrived. I'm upstairs in
bed." And then I thought, "Oh no, now
I've got to go downstairs for food."
I uh I what I really wanted like my
parents have both uh always lived near a
park and I'd always been able to see a
tree out of my bedroom window. So that
became a priority when I was house
hunted. I wanted to be able to see a
tree out of my bedroom window. But it
became very clear that I'm not massively
suited to country living having lived in
the city center for so long. I drove
along a lovely country lane, lovely
country lane, and I saw a white marquee
tent. And instead of thinking, "Oh,
somebody's having a lovely summer
party." I just thought, "Oh, someone's
been murdered."
But I found a house that I liked and I
got a survey done. The survey came back
and it meant nothing to me at all. But
luckily, I've got a friend who's a
builder and he said, "Let me have a look
at him." I put it into layman's terms. I
said, "Smash it." And it gives a year if
you own your own home.
>> Gives a G if you rent.
See, up to this point, I'd only ever
rented. And I think there are phrases
that mean nothing to those of us who
rent that the rest of you understand cuz
my friend the builder said there is one
thing you will need. I said oh yeah
what's that? He said you'll need a damp
proof course. And I genuinely said I
haven't got time to go to college.
But one of the things the house that I
bought did have is a log burner. I've
never had a log burner before. I got
quite excited by the log burner. Not as
excited as my fellow did. He went, "Oh
my god, we'll be able to get a toasting
fork and we'll be able to toast things."
And I thought, he does know I've got a
toaster, doesn't he? But he went off to
work. I went straight out and bought a
toast and fork. I was too excited. I
came back in with it. I grabbed a loaf
of bread and I thought, I'm just going
to sit in front and work me way through.
Bloody love toast.
Couldn't get it to work. I rang him and
I said, "I can't get it to work." He
said, "How can it not work? It's fire
and bread. How can it not work?" So, I
told him what I've been doing. Turns out
I should have had the little door open.
I might as well be lying slices of bread
on top me radiator.
But when I moved, I had bits and bobs of
furniture. Not much, but I had some
stuff and I was trying to work out what
would best go where'. And I said to me,
"Fell, I got to wish I had a tape
measure." He said, "What do you need a
tape measure for?" I said, "I just want
to know if that unit will fit in that al
cove." He said, "Well, I'll sort that
out for you." I said, "Have you got a
tape measure?" He said, "No, no, it's
just I'm good at that sort of thing." I
said, "What do you mean?" He said, "It's
just an instinct I've got." And first of
all, I thought, "Rubbish." And then I
thought, "Let's have a look." And I
thought, "This is quite a manly thing to
be able to do. If you can do this, maybe
we'll see what else slots wear.
So, go on then do it. And this is what
you did. It went exactly like this.
>> I said, "Is that it? You could got your
[\h__\h] out and done 6 in. 6 in. 6 in. 6
in."
>> I wouldn't I wouldn't go down on a man
with a vagina. All absolutely not. All
on a man. No. No. No. No. No. Because a
man's vagina would be disgusting. Like I
think it's a good thing that most women
are born with them because you look
after stuff like men. Oh, no thank you.
No, no, no, no, no. People get so angry
though, man. Like I uh I always used to
say the LGBT community and then someone
threw a bottle at me for not saying
LGBTQIA+
and it's like mate, I'm on your team. I
just didn't know. Like I didn't miss you
out deliberately. Give people some
credit. You've named your community
after a bloody Welsh village. I'm not
gonna
get everything right first time. Like,
also, does anyone know what the A stands
for in LGBTQIA? The A, anyone? Asexual.
Yeah. Now, that baffles me somewhat.
Like, I don't understand why those
people would want to be part of the same
group because that means a gay pride.
You've got people who are like, I'm not
ashamed. I'm proud. I'm a man and I love
men. You know, I'm a woman. I have sex
with women. And then you got these
people at the back WHO ARE LIKE, I WANT
NO PART OF THIS FILTH. like
holding up a blank placard like
nothing. WE WANT NOTHING. YOU'RE like
over there. It's a different march in
it. Surely
the problem with some sexist stereotypes
though is that they're there for a
reason, aren't they? Some questions can
only be answered with a stereotype. For
example, there's a stereotype that women
can multitask and that MEN ARE JUST LIKE
THE WHOLE TIME.
I think it's offensive to men more than
anything. But some questions can only be
answered with a stereotype. For example,
why is it why is it that you never hear
about a woman who died wanking?
It's exclusively a male method of death,
isn't it? the rope around the neck and
only the Now this makes no sense because
women masturbate. We know this. Women
have masturbated since the 1980s. Of
course,
I believe it was the sinking of the
Belgrano that finally got them going.
[snorts]
Now, statistically, there must exist
women that like to strangle themselves
to increase the size of their orgasm,
but you never hear about them because
they don't die doing it. Women seem to
be able to strangle themselves and
masturbate at the same time. You know
why? because they can multitask, you
see.
AND MEN'S LIKE, "AH, YOU'RE GOING TO
DIE. [\h__\h] IT." AND THEY DIE. SO,
some questions can only be answered with
a stereotype. That's my point. But these
stereotypes were obviously used in the
past to kind of make life harder for
women. But, uh, now some people think
maybe life is harder for men because of
the whole me too movement. I don't know
about that. But what I do know is that
no man could deal with the me too
hashtag. Like no, not even the really
woke liberal good guys. Like I've got a
friend who's a real good guy, you know,
like like one of them. And he um he's
always blogging about why we can't eat
prawns or something. Nonsense. And uh
he's like, "OH, THIS HARASSMENT STUFF'S
TERRIBLE, ISN'T IT? HARASSMENT STUFF."
OH, makes you want to castrate yourself.
What?
That's what he said. Every man should
just castrate himself. It's like, come
on, mate. That's such a male response,
isn't it? Cuz women still want to have
sex. They just don't want to be
harassed. Right. So if women are like,
"Hey, could you stop harassing us?" AND
MEN GO, "OH, RIGHT. I SEE. WELL, I GUESS
I DON'T NEED THIS ANYMORE. SHOCK."
Surely women are like, "No, I still want
to have sex just more on my terms." But
then we're like, "No, no, those are your
options.
Either we can harass YOU OR IT'S
NOTHING. THE SPECIES ENDS. PICK A TEAM,
KAREN.
>> [applause]
>> I like the mix of different people that
we get in the UK. I don't agree with
UKIP. UKIP say we got too many
foreigners in this country. I done a bit
of research on my own and the fact is
there's actually a lot more foreigners
in other countries.
I agree with you on the Euro. I don't
think we should get the euro. I think
that'll be bad for business. I mean,
Poundland's buggered.
I think we got it pretty good in the UK
is what I think. But people still love
to complain in it. ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
NO. WHAT'S WRONG? My phone battery died.
Are you all right? No. I'm well stressed
about what I'm going to wear. H. Are you
all right? No. Got like irritable
bowels. What do you think people
complain about them sorts of things in
countries where they don't have
everything that we does? I mean, can you
imagine the children in need appeal? And
you got scenes all across Africa. You
got the cheesy charity music in the
background. You got Dean Gaffne looking
emotional down the camera.
Got an African child next to him.
[snorts]
And Baisy is just 12 years of age.
And Baisy is just another victim here in
Africa. And Baisy needs your help.
And Baisy
is gluten intolerant.
And if he attempts to eat rice or bread
or certain types of musli,
he gets a slightly BLOATED FEEL IN HIS
TUMMY.
Please give generously.
2 allowing Baisy to buy some gluten-free
hummus.
5 will allow him to have the time he
needs to regularly tweet about his
condition.
And 20 will mean Baisy can make the
lifechanging visit he needs to Holland
and Barrett.
[applause]
I got to get going. I got to get out of
here. Yeah, I'm proper knackered, man.
When you have a kid, kiss goodbye to
sleep. That is for sure, people. Last
night about 4:00 in the morning, I'm
spark out in my bed. I'm in there and it
little boy comes into me room. Daddy.
Daddy.
Yeah. Can I come and sleep in your bed?
I've wet my bid.
Of course you can. In you come. Now I
warn you, I've had too much to drink and
I've done the same myself.
Whenever I talk about my proca punch,
there's always a very specific laugh in
the audience. I've learned to recognize
it. It's just over there tonight. It's
this. [laughter]
And I know what it is now. That is the
laugh of a thin yoga woman.
And I know what the laugh means. LAUGH
WAS LIKE, "THAT'S FUNNY, BUT I'D kill
myself if I look like you."
But I promise you, there's advantages to
having a procco punch. MAKE SOME NOISE
IF YOU GOT ONE. [cheering]
>> Two female laugh for the bodies in the
room.
>> Don't be shy, lads. I can see you. It's
quite well lit.
>> Let's try that again. We're all being
honest about ourselves. Give us a cheer
if YOU GOT A PROCCO PORCH.
BOYS, BOYS, BOYS.
The thing is, if you have a procco
punch, there are advantages to it,
right? Two main ones I can think of.
Number one, I don't want to be crude,
but I can take some hammer.
Yeah. Yeah, it's true. I can give you a
list of names that can attest to that as
well,
not surnames.
Now, the other thing is my proca porch
always GIVES ME THE GREATEST slice of
joy, right? You know those three
incredibly hot days we get that we pass
off as the summer, right? I absolutely
love those because that's when I get all
my tanning done. I'm take it very
seriously. I go and get a chair from the
kitchen. I go and put it slap bang in
the middle of my garden, right? Cuz all
the sun hits there. I've not got outdoor
furniture. I'm not a Tory. So I pop it
there
and then I get as uh I get as naked as
is legally possible. So I've got full
spananiel's ears out. Smallest knickers
I can find. You might be worrying about
me now because this is obviously filmed
in London. I live in the countryside.
I've not really got neighbors. I've got
one lad who can see into my garden. He's
depressed. He's not looking out his
window for three weeks. We're fine,
right?
I also get very precious when I'm doing
my tanning, right? Very precious. So,
what I'll do is I'll um I roll my
knickers down as small as I can get them
cuz I'm like, I don't want tan lines.
Actually, I don't want tan lines. I got
a bush like a badger, BUT I DON'T WANT
TAN LINES. IT'S GOT TV. I DON'T WANT TAN
LINES. I'm not allowed no cows.
So, I lie there drinking it in. And as I
lie there, think to myself, you know
what? I am going to get up AND I AM
GOING TO GO TO the freezer and I am
going to treat myself to a third magnum
of the day
cuz I'm a special princess and I do
deserve it.
[cheering] Thank you
for all the people who are allowed ice
cream up there in that one section.
Lactose intolerant in the stores,
closer to the toilets. It makes sense.
So, I'll decide I'm going to treat
myself to that magnum. And then I'll
wait another 40 minutes till I can
actually be asked to get up and get it.
And then when I get up and get it, this
is where my procco podge really steps
up. BECAUSE AS I STAND UP, I WILL HEAR
THE sound of my own gunt peeling off the
top of my own leg.
Yeah. Don't go uh Don't pretend you're
not turned on. It's embarrassing.
It's an incredible noise. It's like
this.
That's my mating call.
It is. I just hear bald heads along the
fence like that.
Just divorced dads who are like, "Is
that low self-esteem?" I can hear.
Do you want to come to Pizza Hut and be
a mum for two hours?
>> I hated teaching and it's a brilliant,
wonderful, noble profession. Obviously,
teaching. I hated it cuz I didn't want
to do it. The only thing that got me
through those years were children
because some of you parents will know
children are wonderful and
weird.
I used to teach a class in North London.
You'll think I'm exaggerating this. I'm
not. This is just one class I'm talking
about. They were the strangest group of
human beings I have ever seen assembled
in one place. Right? They were the
strangest group of human beings ever in
one. And I include all of the series of
Big Brother in that. Right, I'll talk
you through some of them. There was a
child called Marwood in that class,
which isn't a real name, let's be
honest. He was absolutely on a different
planet to the rest of us. I'll prove it.
I once said to him, "Marwood, what are
you going to do when you leave school?"
Straight away, he said, "Well, I'm going
to be one of two things, sir. I'm going
to be a gynecologist or a train driver."
I said, "They're rather contrasting
professions, Marwood. This is only funny
if you believe me." Wasn't trying to be
funny at this point. He went, "Yeah,
yeah, they are, aren't they, sir?" I
suppose at the end of the day, I just
like tunnels.
Fortunately, there was a child in that
class that made up for all of them. Her
name was Karen Pal. She was my favorite
student of all time. She was 11 years of
age, this big, and had two fascinating
characteristics. Number one, her
internal compass was buggered, right?
So, she was 10 minutes late to every
single lesson, and the school wasn't
that big. 10 minutes late. The second
was even though she was 11, she spoke
for reasons best known to our creator
like an repressed 1940s housewife.
And if I'm exaggerating this, I am not
exaggerating it. She would come into my
class like this. Hello, sir. How are you
today?
I say, I'm fine, thanks. Karen, how are
you? SHE GOES, YES, I'M VERY WELL,
THANKS.
I MUST SAY, I'M VERY MUCH LOOKING
FORWARD TO TODAY'S IMPROVISATION.
I'll give you an example of her compass.
She came to see me after a lesson. This
is more verbatim quote. She went,
"Excuse me, sir. Can I have a word with
you, please?" "Well, of course, you can
carry on. What's the problem?" She goes,
"I just wanted to say that I thought my
performance in your lesson today was a
little below par."
I said, "Really? I thought you were
great." "No, no. I thought my use of
characterization was paper thin. Thought
the way I moved around the space was
appalling. And my group work was
something to be condemned. and I would
like to offer you my most humble of
apologies.
I said, "You listen to me, Karen Pal.
You never need to apologize to me. You
are my favorite pupil because you make
me laugh my head off."
Now go outside and enjoy your lunchtime.
You've deserved it. She said, "You know
what? I think I will."
I turned round at that point to do a
little bit of admin. Ladies and
gentlemen, Karen was then faced with a
choice. She could leave my room via the
only exit
or she could go into my costume
cupboard.
I don't know what happened, but for
safety, I'll tell you this. I locked my
costume cupboard before I went for my
lunch. Then I went away for a whole
hour. When I came back, I opened the
cupboard and I swear to you, that child
was standing with her back to me in a
scene from the Diddy Man remake of the
Blair Witch Project just doing this.
AND I WENT, SHE WENT, "HELLO, SIR."
I SAID, "HAVE YOU BEEN IN THERE FOR A
WHOLE HOUR?" SHE SAID, "I'M RATHER
AFRAID I HAVE."
I said, "OH MY GOD, I AM SO SORRY." SHE
SAID, "DON'T you apologize to me. I'VE
ONLY GOT MYSELF TO BLAME. I'LL SEE YOU
LATER.
[applause]
>> The most sexually adventurous thing I
ever did, I did it when I was single.
When I was single, I ordered the number
one vibrator on the Love Honey website.
And the Love Honey website is a sex toy
website for those of you pretending not
to know.
I kind of ordered it out of spite,
right? Because one of my exes called me
approved, which I think is such an
extreme thing to call someone. I don't
think I did anything to warrant that.
The only thing I can think of maybe is
once I said that I don't like morning
sex. That's not a big deal. That doesn't
mean that I'm not sex positive. I just
don't think you should do something that
disgusting in the morning.
Not whilst the blackbird is singing his
morning tune.
[laughter]
But I went on the website. It was late
at night. I just ordered the first one
on the list cuz I thought that will be
good. That will probably be quite nice.
The thing that arrived is so terrifying.
It plugs directly into the wall.
It has one of those on the end of it. It
uses mains electricity.
It needs to be pat tested.
I just find that so threatening cuz I
think what that's basically saying is
what I'm about to do to you
couldn't possibly be done with a
battery.
I'm going to need that same stuff that
powers your fridge.
It's huge. It's bigger than this. It
looks like a piece of farming equipment
from the industrial revolution.
But it's called a wand. There is nothing
magical about it. I've never seen this
type of vibrator before. All the
vibrators that I've seen advertised
online are very small and portable and
they're not making big claims. They're
just happy to live in your bedside
drawer and they'll be there like, "Okay,
girl. I'm here if you need me." Like, if
you and your partner get like super
super drunk one night, maybe you could
experiment with me for a little bit.
Honestly, I might not do anything, but I
might speed things along for you a
little bit. Either way, no worries if
not. Whereas my vibrator is just next to
the BED LIKE, "DO YOU WANT TO MEET GOD?
>> [laughter]
>> NOT REALLY. It doesn't even fit in the
bedside drawer. It's just curled up on
the floor like a python.
And after it arrived, I was like, "Is
this the right thing?" Cuz I checked on
the website cuz I thought maybe it got
mixed up with like an order meant for
Guantanamo Bay.
It was the right thing. Not only that, I
read the description for the first time.
It said in the description, "This is the
world's most powerful vibrator."
I don't think I need that. I need
absolute max. A whisper on the wind.
The world's most powerful vibrator. You
shouldn't be able to buy that without a
license.
Underneath as well, it said, "The
vibrator will turn off automatically
after 20 minutes for your safety."
21 minutes. And there's a danger of
death.
I can't even I don't even want to sh It
cost £90.
So, I felt like I had to try it because
I spent so much money and I I don't I
don't even have a plug next to my bed. I
had to get the extension cable.
That felt desperate.
I turned it on onto the lowest setting.
It had a settings. I turned it on to
setting one. [groaning]
It was so loud. I was like, there's
nothing private about this experience.
The neighbors are going to think I'm
having a new kitchen put in. At
midnight, they're going to call the
council. Well, no, they're not calling
anyone. They don't have any power right
now.
I tried it just for like one maybe two
seconds and I was like, I can smell
burning.
I can't use this thing. It's going to
sand me down. It's going to erode. I'm
going to be flat over. There'll be
nothing left like Barbie.
But it had eight settings.
I thought, I have to see what setting 8
does. Not on myself. I know my limits. I
just turned it up to setting eight in
the sky. [\h__\h] me. I was like, I'm going
to rip a hole in the space-time
continuum.
The cable was the more middle class
option. Yes. No, we don't want a
satellite dish sticking out the side of
our house. No, thank you. I think it
looks really quite naff. Yeah. Whereas
the working class, the satellite dish
was the key selling point.
If you're paying £25 a month, you want
your neighbors to know
that you are better than them.
And we had Sky through a dish 1997. You
could be watching Old School Sky in the
living room, watching it on the main TV,
but you could also go upstairs to the
bedroom TVs, turn to a certain channel,
and watch Sky in the bedroom, but only
what the person in the living room
was watching. I don't know the intrinsic
technical explanation as to why this
happened, but it just did.
Saturday nights, me and my dad. I'm on
the couch. He's in his chair. My mom's
in bed. My brother's out with his pals.
Just me and the old man watching match
of the day, watching the highlights. It
gets to the kind of shite games. And I
say, "Right, I think I'm [snorts] I
think I'm going to go to bed, Dad.
Good night.
And he would continue the sherad and he
said, "Are you off to bed, son? Good
night."
And there was that mutual father and
son. We both know what the plan is here.
I would I would casually exit the living
room nice and slowly. Good night. Hit
the hallway and race up the stairs.
Don't even consider looking in the
fridge. Eyes on the prize.
Upstairs. Bedroom TV switched on. Go to
number six. That's you see what he's
watching. TVs are synchronized. Six.
We're in. He's in control.
A few minutes go by and he's still
watching match of the day. That's fine.
He must be giving it a few minutes. You
don't want to make it too obvious.
He's done this before.
Five minutes go by. He's still watching
match of the day. I'm thinking, come on,
stick to the plan. Andy,
I'm looking at the bottom left of the
screen, waiting for the numbers to get
typed in.
The numbers that could make or break the
evening's entertainment.
Give me your numbers, Andy. Come on.
Nine. That's a good start. Nine.
Could
not have hoped for a better start than a
nine. Now
05 the 10-minute free view.
You're a dirty bastard, Dad. But I love
you.
[applause]
So, we've got some celebrities in as
always live at Apollo. Who have we got?
Who have we got? We've got the
EastEnders cast. How we doing, East
Enders?
Sitting right at the back. I don't mean
the extras. I mean the real people.
[applause]
We're trying to get Phil Mitchell. No.
Where is he? He's up at He's up at
King's Cross dressed up as a a lady boy
trying to raise enough money to buy a
corn.
ARE
>> THERE ANY WELSH PEOPLE OUT THERE?
[cheering]
>> TELL THEM
TELL THEM HOW GOOD IT IS NOW.
>> OH, IT'S NOT [\h__\h] ANYMORE. WE SPENT
MILLIONS, SO IT'S NOT [\h__\h] FOR YOU.
THAT'S THE WHOLE WELSH PEOPLE, WHERE ARE
YOU FROM?
FAIR ENOUGH [\h__\h]
[applause]
>> YEAH,
I'm trying TO EXPLAIN THAT THE PLACE HAS
IMPROVED AND YOU LOB SWANSEA and Duster
is Swansea still a desperate dump, isn't
it? Let's face it, devoid of any hope
whatsoever. Swansea, have you been?
There's a sign on the way in that says,
"Kill our children, not your speed."
Isn't there is there
[applause]
I'M TALKING ABOUT PLACES LIKE CARDIFF
AND THE PLACES THAT HAVE YES. THESE
PLACES HAVE IMPROVED. WE'VE HAD
DEVELOPMENT MONEY. WE'VE DONE CARDIFF
BAY. HAVE YOU BEEN THERE? GO THERE ON
HOLIDAY. It's lovely. WE'VE DONE IT ALL
UP. YOU'VE GOT CAFES AND BARS. YOU GOT
THE SEA DOWN THERE NOW. IT'S AMAZING.
SHOOT DOWN WHERE THE [\h__\h] WAS. THAT'S
ALL SEA NOW. MOST OF IT. AND it's going
to be AMAZING WHEN THEY FINISH IT. Has
anybody seen the posters OF WHAT CARDIFF
BAY IS GOING TO BE LIKE WHEN IT'S ALL
DONE?
>> It's not. IT'S GOING TO BE AMAZING.
THERE'S GOING TO BE people chatting,
LAUGHING, TEXTING WELSH PEOPLE. THESE
ARE PRESUMABLY HAVING INTERESTING
CONVERSATIONS OVER DINNER. WE'RE ALL
GOING TO BE A LOT BETTER LOOKING BY THE
TIME IT'S FINISHED AS WELL. YOU LOOK
OUT. Where they going to get THESE
PEOPLE WITH FASHIONABLE GLASSES AND
TEETH FROM IN CARDIFF? I GOT NO IDEA.
You've got to admire their optimism,
HAVEN'T YOU, FLY? [laughter]
TALKING OF OPTIMISM, YOU GOT CARDIFF
BAY. I WAS THERE NOT LONG AGO. SOME OF
SOME OF THESE RESTAURANTS, SOME OF THEM
HAVE GOT TABLES OUTSIDE.
FRESCO DINING IN CARDIFF. THEY'RE HAVING
A LAUGH ON ME. I TRIED TO HAVE A TWIX AT
A BUS STOP IN WALES A FEW YEARS AGO. IT
WAS it was too wet TO EAT TO BE HONEST
WITH YOU. EVERYBODY'S PRETENDING IT'S
MADRID. COME ON, WE'LL SIT OUTSIDE. YOUR
SOUP BOWLS FILLING UP FASTER THAN YOU
CAN EAT IT FOR CHRIST SAKE. STOP
RAINING.
You'll never GET PAST YOUR STARTERS
AFTER 7 HOURS OF SOUP AND RAIN WATER YOU
GIVE UP. SUE YOUR GIN AND TONICS
OVERFLOWING. A LITTLE UMBRELLA'S BLOWN
INSIDE OUT. TURN IT BACK INTO THE WIND.
TURN IT BACK INTO THE WIND.
IT'S WAITERS WITH FROSTED EYEBROWS
FIGHTING THEIR WAY TO THE TABLE.
SPAGHETTI CARBONARA. SPAGHETTI
CARBONARA. [screaming] SURE. I'LL GET
ANOTHER ONE. I'LL GET ANOTHER ONE. AS
PEOPLE THROW IN LIFE BOYS TO THEIR BREAD
ROLLS. I'LL PULL YOU IN. I'LL PULL YOU
IN. PEAS BEING AIRLIFTED TO SAFETY.
OH, Wales is improving. Even the
valleys. Go to the valleys on holiday.
EVEN THE VALLEYS. THEY ARE. SHUT YOUR
FACE. THEY'RE GETTING BETTER. THEY'RE
GETTING BETTER. THE WELSH. I DID A GIG
IN in Ponta Pre
in the Welsh valleys. WERE YOU THERE AT
THE GIG I DID WHEN THERE WAS A PIECE OF
SUNDRIED TOMATO ON THE STAGE?
[\h__\h] IN A REAL PIECE OF SUNDRIED
TOMATO.
We couldn't EVEN DO THE GIG. EVERYBODY
WAS JUST STARING AT IT. I COULDN'T GET
THEM. I couldn't get their attention.
That's not local to your area, IS IT?
THE SUNDRIED TOMATO.
HEY, there was a pile up in the valleys
a few years ago cuz somebody mentioned
satsumas. DID YOU READ ABOUT THAT?
SOMEBODY'S TROING THAT, HAVEN'T THEY?
THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENED. THAT'S DO YOU
LIVE HERE NOW, MADAM? IS THAT DO YOU
LIVE HERE? ARE YOU FROM THE VALLEYS?
>> My boyfriend is from THE VALLEYS.
>> YOUR BOYFRIEND WAS PROBABLY HIM THAT
TROTT IN THE SUN-DRIED TOMATO AND
DRAGGED IT ALL THE WAY BACK.
He probably stepped in the sun-dried
tomato in London and took IT ALL THE WAY
BACK TO THE HE MUST HAVE BEEN [\h__\h]
HIMSELF ON THE WAY BACK. THEY'LL KILL
YOU FOR THAT IN PONTA PRE, WON'T THEY?
GET IT OFF ME. THEY'RE GOING TO KILL ME.
THEY'RE GOING TO KILL ME. DITCH THE
SHOE. DITCH THE SHOE.
I just celebrated 9 years of marriage
just the other day. You know what I'm
saying? Yes.
[applause]
>> Thank you guys. Thank you. 9 years
married to the same person. Jesus
Christ, man.
Listen, man. I'm I'm just glad I'm no
longer dating. I'm glad cuz dating right
now is the ghetto. I'm not going to lie
to you. It's not easy to date. And you
know what the thing about dating is?
Every time I see someone out, I'm like,
"How are you affording this?" You know
what I'm saying? It's a cost OF LIVING
CRISIS. WHEN I SEE PEOPLE OUT eating
food, I'm just like, I don't know how
you're doing this. Even I'm on TV and I
still take my wife to the local chip
shop. You know what I'm saying? Like I'm
like, you're not getting this Taskmaster
money. No. Mm-
No, man. The dating back in the day, I
used to get rejected a lot because I'm
short. You know what I'm saying? Short
guys. Yeah. We don't get no love, man.
short guys. The minute I'll be on the
phone talking to girls and I'll be like,
you know, yeah, biz, I want to take you
out. She'll be like, oh my god, how tall
are you? I'll be like, yeah, I'm 5 foot.
Hello. Hello.
I am happy. I am married. And I've got
two wonderful children. Me and my wife
got two beautiful children. Eight and
one. Right now, the 8-year-old, that's a
boy, right? And my boy is crazy. Make
some noise. If you got sons in the
building, make some noise.
>> [cheering]
>> So, you know what I'm talking about.
Boys are crazy, right? It's not just me.
Have you ever just looked at your boy
and been like, "What the hell are you
doing
every day?" All right. My son is
obsessed with superheroes. He loves
superheroes, right? Which is a bit weird
in our household because we're like
devout Christians. Like, especially my
wife, she like we love going to church,
right? My wife is definitely getting
into heaven 100%. Like hopefully I'm her
plus one. I hope. You know, I'm going be
like, "No, I'm with her." No. Okay,
cool. Cool. You know what I'm saying? M.
The reason why I bring that up is cuz
last year Halloween, my son, he wanted
to uh go trick-or-treating, right? Which
is a bit weird in our household. Again,
we're Christians. And he was just like,
"Mom, I want to dress up as a
superhero." And my wife would decide
there is no superhero in this house
other than Jesus Christ.
So she dressed him for Halloween as
Jesus Christ.
This guy went out trick-or-treating,
giving out bread and wine. You know what
I'm saying? Like he was like, "God bless
you." Yeah. God bless you, too. God
bless you.
One day me and my son, we were at home.
We're by ourselves, right? I'm
downstairs. I'm watching TV. My son is
upstairs, right? He's doing whatever
he's doing, right? And it got silent.
And you guys know what happens when it
goes silent with a child. It means
they're doing something they should not
be doing, right? And then out of
nowhere, I hear a loud thud. Just boom.
I'm like, "Oh god, what's that?" And
then my SON'S JUST LIKE, "DADDY."
[screaming]
SO I run to the hallway and my son is
standing at the top of the staircase
dressed in a DIY superhero outfit,
right? And he's just standing there.
He's like, "Look, Dad, I'm a superhero."
And I was like, "Uh-oh." I was like,
"Son, you might want to take that off
before your mom comes home." All right.
And he's just like, "No, Dad. Look, I
can fly." And as soon as he said that,
I'm not going to lie, it got slow motion
in my house. I was like, "No."
And my son was like,
a part of me was just like, "Let me let
him fly so he can break his legs." You
know what I'm saying? And calm down.
But I read this thing right online, so
it must be true. where everyone who's
under the age of 30 is going to live
till 160.
Uh like you look tired now 160.
I don't want to be sat in a flat leaking
LIVER SPOTTED. YOUR EARS AND NOSE THEY
NEVER STOP GROWING. I got to BE SAT
THERE LOOKING LIKE I work at bloody
gringot's bank just like
and I think if I get to 160 I'm ending
it. I don't know how you do it. What you
going to do? sort of suffocate yourself
with a bag for life. I reckon the best
way and maybe like a toaster in a bath
situation, but it' be one of those like
sit down baths with a chair and a door
and then you have to wait for it all to
fill up. You put in a bit of native for
a last bit of luxury. Then you go, "Oh
[\h__\h] I forgot the toaster." And then
you have to WAIT FOR IT ALL to drain.
You open the door, you go out onto the
landing, down a Stennis Airlift, into
the kitchen. You go, "What the bloody
HELL AM I COMING HERE FOR? IT'S NEVER
GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> [applause]
>> I'm trying to do more nice things
though. That's what I'm trying to do
because I've never really done anything
with me life that I did a thing
recently. I went to go and give blood
for the first time. Has anyone ever done
that?
It's one woman. Yeah, I did it today.
It's amazing. But I thought you did it
in like a hospital or like a sanitized
medical center. You don't. You do it in
like a rugby club or like a methodone
church, right?
I turn up to this bingo hall near me
nan's house, right? I was greeted by the
mood, sorry, second moodiest person I've
ever seen in me life. It was a woman
called Linda. Like her name badge said
Jean, but she looked like a Linda. Do
you know what I mean? Like short bob,
gel, fringe, good at darts.
She weren't happy. She weren't I turned
up. She goes, "Have you got an
appointment?" And I went, "Uh, no." And
she goes, "Have you filled out a form?"
And I went, "Uh, no." And then she threw
this form at me. And as I'm walking off,
she goes, "Thank you very much for
giving blood. We really appreciate it.
Giving blood is the greatest gift anyone
could ever receive." And I'm thinking,
Linda's never been given a slow cooker.
Take this form. I start filling it out.
I had to use this woman's eyeliner cuz
Linda wouldn't let me a pen. Just
filling it all out. And as I said, the
only reason I went to go and give blood
is make myself feel like I've done
something with my life. And instead, I'm
faced with all these very serious adult
questions. It was things like, "Have you
ever been to Africa?" And I'm like, "Uh,
no." And he goes, "Have you ever had sex
with a man?" And I'm like, "Uh, no." And
he goes, "Have you ever had sex with a
prostitute?" And I thought, "I've done
[\h__\h] nothing with my life.
NOTHING. HAVE YOU INJECTED DRUGS? HAVE
YOU SMOKEN DRUGS? HAVE YOU HAD ANY
TREATMENTS IN THE LAST 6 MONTHS?" I
PANICKED. WENT, "OH, WELL, me and me mom
have had facials off group on." Not the
right answer. Weirdest question. Are you
HIV positive? I was like, "What? No."
Like, if anything, I'm against it.
And then they took me off into this room
and there's all these like Sharons and
John's lay on beds with sort of needles
in their arms. Like, it looked like a
spa day for smackheads.
Belt around my arm, not even a nice
belt. They spanked it a bit. They told
me to relax. And then they whipped out
the biggest flipping needle I've ever
seen in me life. And I just fainted.
Completely fainted. I can hear all these
muffled voices. And then I can hear
Linda's bellowing voice just going, I
knew he'd be a fainter. I'm like,
by the time I'd come around, all these
people are trying to help me out. And
Linda just parted them. And her way of
trying to make me feel better. Her way
of trying to make me feel like a proper
grown-up was going, "Would you like a
glass of orange juice and a biscuit?" I
was like, "No, Linda. I want to have sex
with an African gay man for money.
That's what I want to do.
[applause]
But I got I got Sky TV now, which is
excellent. You can pause live TV. Just
pause it. The people at home now can
just pause it and it's a perfect pause.
Not the old sort of 1980s VHS pause.
That was a very different story, wasn't
it?
You couldn't even SEE WHAT YOU WERE
WATCHING in 1980s paws. PEOPLE WHO
WEREN'T MOVING WOULD START MOVING EVEN
moving in THIS SCENE. PEOPLE IN
PAINTINGS WOULD COME TO LIFE. I'M GOING
TO PRACTICE.
But then once you pause for it, it's
quite exciting cuz you can watch it back
in like times 2 or 6 or 12 or 30, which
makes boring programs quite
entertaining. Like in the tennis, you
can forward the the changeovers.
Watching Andy Murray eating a banana in
times 12 is quite
I watch Deal or No Deal in Times 30. It
really whizzes along.
I watch all TV. I watch TV just to slack
it off. To be honest, Dragon's Den winds
me right up. I know you're rich,
dragons. You don't need to bring your
cash with you.
THEY SIT THERE WITH CASH ON THEIR
TABLES. I'm so tremendously wealthy. All
my bank accounts are full. I've had to
bring additional funds with me today.
What about you, Theopathetist? Have you
got money on your table? Oh, I'm
completely loaded. I've thrown money up
onto my table. That's every time. What
about you two dragons? Oh, yes, we've
got a lot of cash here. All right, bring
in the first poor person. Let's see what
they've got. They come in trembling.
Hello, trackers.
Please, can I have some cash for the
ideas in my brain?
I feel sick just looking at poor people.
Look at the state of her clothing. For
that reason, I'm out.
What about you, Theopathist? Are you
out? I will be out, but I'm going to
humiliate the [\h__\h] for 15 minutes.
Then I will declare [applause] that I
too am out.
I'd like to dragon with a shotgun just
stand there pointing it at at each of
them individually till one of them goes
to so what's your idea quite simple put
that cash in this bag all right
you get no equity
[applause]
I like some TV I watch it till the
bitter end literally like the early
hours of the morning till the signing
zone the deaf zone that's when you know
it's probably time for bed you know when
there's somebody in the corner signing
You feel a bit like this isn't really
for me.
They always look at you like come on.
You you could have watched this in the
day. It's probably bedtime for you.
Deaf people have been asleep all day to
stay up for this. Have some respect.
I like it when there's no dialogue in
the show and they watch TV with you.
[applause]
I might the other day I was watching the
the blue planet or something. This is a
show with David Atenburgh where they
discover creatures from the depths of
the ocean for the very first time.
Literally fish that were only just
discovered and they were naming them on
the show. So he was going, "Here we have
the newly discovered diploloyicos." And
the tiny guy was going,
he resorted to impersonating the fish.
The fish was swimming. He was just
underneath going,
[applause]
I've got the memory of an elephant. I
remember one time I went to the zoo and
saw an elephant.
I was disappointed to find that Dunk
Kirk wasn't actually a biography of
William Shatner.
I accidentally kicked my dog earlier and
it bit me on the bollocks. My mate said
it's karma. I said no. If anything, it's
even more angry.
I tell you what always catches my eye.
Short people with umbrellas.
I put on a lot of weights. I rang up
Weight Watchers. I said, "It's an
emergency. Can you send somebody
around?" And they said, "Yes, we can. We
got loads of them.
I was actually thrown out of weight
watchers for making sarcastic comments
at the weekly weigh-in. As you can
imagine, I accepted the decision with
huge grace cuz they threw her out as
well.
I was watching TV. The announcer said
there's a documentary about the clitoris
on the red button, but I couldn't find
it.
>> [applause]
>> I was in a fancy lingerie shop. I said,
"Are these knickers sat in?" He said,
"No, they're new."
I didn't know what to get my little
niece for Christmas. So, I asked my
sister what she's into. Apparently, at
the moment, she's mad about frozen
stuff. So, I got her some oven chips and
peas.
It's been a tough week. I got myself a
memory foam mattress and now it's trying
to blackmail me.
[laughter]
As a child, I was made to walk the
plank. We couldn't afford a dog.
I went on a positive thinking course. It
was [\h__\h]
You would be. And it was half empty.
The area in a Nando between the front
and back door is called the Perry
Perneium.
What I like most about that joke
is that people who know what a paranium
is usually haven't heard of Nandos.
Ironically, there's only a very small
overlap between the two.
The doctor told me to lose some weight.
I said, "How?" He said, "Don't eat
anything fatty." I said, "What? Pies?
chips, that sort of thing. He said, "No,
just don't eat anything fatty."
Old lady names are very much back in
fashion at the minute, like Lily or
Elsie or Rose. And we wanted something
like that for our daughter, but we
couldn't decide. So, in the end, we just
called her Nan.
So, we should grow into it.